Kajal Gupta

Digital Marketer

Urban Estate Gurgaon, Haryana 122001 hi@kajalgupta.com 8689039420

Kajal is a Digital Marketer with over 1 year of experience.

She has worked in the following domains: WP Website Administration, Search Engine Optimization, Social Media Marketing, Content Marketing, Email Marketing, and Analytics.

Tools she's well acquainted with: WordPress, Google Search Console, Google Analytics, MailChimp, HubSpot, Elementor, Unbounce, SwipePages, PowToon, Canva, Vidiq, Grammarly, Slider Revolution, Google Trends, Google Alerts, SEMrush, Ahrefs, Ubersuggest, Facebook Ads Manager, Ads library, etc.

Please find my portfolio at the end of the resume.

Work Experience

Digital Marketing Executive

Grablor Technologies February 2021 to May 2021

Worked on WordPress, SEO, SMM, Content Marketing, Email Marketing, Analytics, PPC, SEM, Google Adwords, etc.

Digital Marketing Intern

Labdox

October 2020 to January 2021

My Responsibilities involved Digital Marketing, SEO, SMO, SMM, Content Marketing & Email Marketing.

Digital Marketing Intern

Spoken English World

December 2020 to December 2020

Provided Services in SEO, Website Analysis, Website Management, Tracking & Conversion.

Social Media Marketing Intern

LUDIFU

October 2020 to October 2020

Worked in the following categories: Social Media Marketing, Marketing Specialist, Business Development.

Pharmaceutical Content Writing Intern

Seek2Share Technologies June 2018 to August 2018

I had interned with the company's brand Smart Medics as a content writer in their marketing team.

Education

Bachelor's in English Literature

Maharishi Dayanand University, Rohtak - Gurgaon, Haryana July 2016 to May 2019

Higher Secondary(12th Pass) in Non-medical (PCM)

Aravali public school, Haryana April 2014 to March 2016

Secondary(10th Pass)

Aravali public school, Haryana April 2012 to March 2014

Skills / IT Skills

- Digital Marketing
- Google Analytics
- Google Search Console
- · Social Media Marketing
- Email Marketing
- SMO
- Content Marketing
- · Google Ads Search
- Analytics
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- MailChimp
- Blogging
- WordPress

Languages

- English Fluent
- Hindi Fluent

Online Profile

https://kajalgupta.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kajalguptadotcom/

Certificate of Participation INSPIRE-2014

December 2014

I had attended five days fully residential Inspire(Innovation in Science Pursuit for Inspired Research)-Internship programme(science camp) 2014 at Om Institute of Technology and Management, Hisar (Haryana), which was 4th Internship programme sponsored by Department of Science and Technology, Government of India, New Delhi.

हृदिरीतन पर्मणपत्र

March 2013

'महत्स्नाधा रेषिटरभषा हृदि पारिचरा ससंथ'|दवरा आयिजोति कि नीई 'अखला भिरातयी रषाटरभषा | गिधा हृदिरितत परकीष(द्वितियी सनत)' म परिथम शरणे पाउँ तत्रीण हनों के उपलक्षय म यह परमणपतर मझ परदन कया निय हूं।

Certificate of Selection at TeckFly

July 2017

I was selected among a chosen few at TeckFly, to write tech related content.

Intern of the Month

November 2020

I was twice awarded *Intern of the Month* by Labdox, for my efforts in digital marketing for their company and their food tech brand Sattv.

Certifications and Licenses

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

September 2020 to Present

SQL, **HTML**, **Python 3**, C++ **Fundamentals**

May 2017 to Present

Google Analytics for Beginners

September 2020 to September 2023

Coding Fundamentals I & II

Present

Search Engine Optimization

September 2020 to Present

Google Ads Search

January 2021 to January 2022

Advanced Google Analytics

January 2021 to January 2024

Google Analytics Individual Qualification

Assessments

Data Analysis — Proficient

October 2020

Interpreting and producing graphs, identifying trends and drawing justifiable conclusions from data.

Full results: Proficient

Attention to Detail — Proficient

September 2020

Finding differences, following instructions, and noticing details among distracting information.

Full results: Proficient

Written Communication — Highly Proficient

September 2020

Best practices for writing, including grammar, style, clarity and brevity.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Logic & Critical Thinking — Highly Proficient

January 2021

Using logic to solve problems. Full results: <u>Highly Proficient</u>

Working with MS Word Documents (Basic) — Highly Proficient

January 2021

Understanding basic word processing functions.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Verbal Communication — Expert

October 2020

Speaking clearly, correctly and concisely.

Full results: Expert

Project Management Skills: Time Management — Proficient

November 2020

Prioritising and allocating time to effectively achieve project deliverables.

Full results: Proficient

Basic Spreadsheets with Microsoft Excel — Proficient

November 2020

Understanding basic Microsoft Excel techniques, such as sorting and filtering.

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

NGO, Non-Profit / Student Organizations

The English Club

May 2012 to March 2016

I was a member of The English Club -a student organisation of my school which was responsible for all the co- curriculars and extracurricular activities like Plays, Poetries, Skits, Quizzes, Debates, Extempore and other events organised for strengthening the Spoken English skills in the students.

Projects / Papers Presented

Portfolio

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1b10bw_4Rqn8ARCAAGx1vW2QVo0Qa31be?usp=sharing
A collection of my past works that demonstrates my expertise. These are assignments from the past internships, & projects taken as a Freelancer.

Additional Information

- Please check out my projects with Grablor Technologies- @moonwake_exotica & @appio.me on Instagram
- Past Industries: Healthcare Edtech Food
- Current Industries: Marketing Hospitality IT
- Preferred mode of communication- Email or Chat
- Preferred location- Work from Home